https://www.qsa-global.com/privacy-policy?hsLang=en

OpenVision DX
Other Devices:
Last Modified: November 16, 2019
We at QSA Global, Inc. (QSA Global, Inc., and our affiliates) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to the information and data collected by QSA Global, Inc. on our Website (qsa-global.com) or through other channels as described below. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the data QSA Global, Inc. processes on behalf of our customers (Customer Data) in our capacity as a processor.
We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at sentinelsales@qsa-global.com or by mail to QSA Global, Inc., 40 North Avenue Burlington, MA 01803 Attn: Privacy.
Information We Collect
When You Visit our Website
You are free to explore the Website without providing any Personal Information about yourself. When you visit the Website to fill out a contact form, we request that you provide Personal Information about yourself, and we collect Navigational Information.
"Personal Information"
This refers to any information that you voluntarily submit to us and that identifies you personally, including contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, company name, address, phone number, and other information about yourself or your business. Personal Information can also include information that you enter into on the Website, and information about you that is available on the internet, such as from Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter and Google, or publicly available information that we acquire from service providers.
Personal Information includes Navigational Information where such information can directly or indirectly identify an individual. Navigational information refers to information about your computer and your visits to the Website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and pages viewed. Please see the "Use of Navigation Information" section below.
Log Files
When you view content provided by us, we automatically collect information about your computer hardware and software. This information can include your IP address, browser type, domain names, internet service provider (ISP), the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, clickstream data, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by QSA Global, Inc. to provide general statistics regarding use of the Website. For these purposes, we do link this automatically-collected data to Personal Information such as name, email address, address, and phone number.
Information we collect from third parties
From time to time, we may receive Personal Information about you from third party sources including partners with which we offer co-branded services or engage in joint marketing activities, and publicly available sources such as social media.
Information About Children
The Website is not intended for or targeted at children under 16, and we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information about children under 16 If you believe that we have collected information about a child under 16, please contact us at privacy@QSA Global, Inc..com, so that we may delete the information.
How We Use Information We Collect
Compliance with Our Privacy Policy
We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy.
We Never Sell Personal Information
We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.
Use of Personal Information
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to:
improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Website to your interests;
send information or QSA Global, Inc. content to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business;
promote use of our products to you and share promotional and information content with you in accordance with your communication preferences;
send information to you regarding changes to our Privacy Policy (including the Cookie Policy), or other legal agreements;
meet legal requirements.
Legal basis for processing Personal Information (EEA visitors only)
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.
Use of Navigational Information
We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Website. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about QSA Global, Inc.
Customer Testimonials and Comments
We post customer testimonials and comments on our Website, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting the customer's name and testimonial.
Security of your Personal Information
We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.  Your Personal Information may also be stored by a third-party. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures.
Social Media Features
Our Website includes Social Media Features, such as the Share Button. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features.  Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.
External Websites
Our Website provides links to other Websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other Websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other Websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other Websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.
Retention of Personal Information
How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information as described in further detail below.  After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.
We retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we securely delete the information or anonymise it or, if this is not possible, securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. We will delete this information at an earlier date if you so request, as described in the "How to Access & Control Your Personal Data" below.
If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our content, products, or services, such as when you last opened an email from us.  We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.
How we Share Information we Collect
Service Providers
We employ other companies and people to provide services to visitors to our Website and our customers and users of the Subscription Service and may need to share your information with them to provide information, products or services to you. Examples may include removing repetitive information from prospect lists, analyzing data or performing statistical analysis, providing marketing assistance, supplementing the information you provide us in order to provide you with better service, and providing customer service or support. In all cases where we share your information with such agents, we explicitly require the agent to acknowledge and adhere to our privacy and customer data handling policies.
QSA Global, Inc. Partners
In addition, we may share data with trusted partners and distributors to contact you based on your request to receive such communications, help us perform statistical analysis, or provide customer support. Such third parties are prohibited from using your Personal Information except for these purposes, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Corporate Events
If we (or our assets) are acquired by another company, whether by merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or otherwise, that company would receive all information gathered by QSA Global, Inc. on the Website. In this event, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your Personal Information, and choices you may have regarding your Personal Information.
Compelled Disclosure
We reserve the right to use or disclose your Personal Information if required by law or if we reasonably believe that use or disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or comply with a law, court order, or legal process.
International Transfer of Information
International Transfers within QSA Global, Inc.’s Entities
To facilitate our global operations, we transfer information to either Czechia or the United States and allow access to that information from countries in which the QSA Global, Inc. affiliated entities have operations for the purposes described in this policy.
This Privacy Policy shall apply even if we transfer Personal Information to other countries. We have taken appropriate safeguards to require that your Personal Information will remain protected. When we share information about you within and among QSA Global, Inc.’s affiliated entities, we make use of standard contractual data protection clauses.
International transfers to third parties
Some of the third parties described in this privacy policy, which provide services to us under contract, are based in other countries that may not have equivalent privacy and data protection laws to the country in which you reside. When we share information of customers in the European Economic Area or Switzerland, we make use of the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks, European Commission-approved standard contractual data protection clauses, binding corporate rules for transfers to data processors, or other appropriate legal mechanisms to safeguard the transfer. Please see our Privacy Shield Notice below.
Privacy Shield Notice
QSA Global, Inc. participates in the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at https://www.privacyshield.gov .
QSA Global, Inc. is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. QSA Global, Inc. complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.
With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, QSA Global, Inc. is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, QSA Global, Inc. may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
Cookies and Related Technologies
Cookies
QSA Global, Inc. and its partners use cookies or similar technologies (such as web beacons) to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. To find out more about how we use cookies on our Website and how to manage your cookie preferences please see our Cookie Policy.
Advertising
We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect information about your activities on this and other Website to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here: http://preferences.truste.com/ (or if located in the European Union, by clicking here: http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.
Third Party Tracking Technologies
The use of cookies and web beacons by any tracking utility company is not covered by our Privacy Policy or Cookie Policy.
How to Access & Control Your Personal Data
Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information
You have the following data protection rights:
You can request access, correction, updates or deletion of your personal information.
You can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information.
If we have collected and processed your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA, Switzerland and certain non-European countries (including the US and Canada) are available here.
To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at sentinelsales@qsa-global.com or by mail to QSA Global, Inc., Inc., 40 North Avenue Burlington, MA 01803 USA, Attention: Privacy. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable time frame and notify you of the action we have taken.
To Unsubscribe From Our Communications
You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of our e-mails, updating your communication preferences, or by sending us email us at sentinelsales@qsa-global.com or postal mail to QSA Global, Inc., 40 North Avenue Burlington, MA 01803, Attention: Privacy.
To Unsubscribe from Our Customers' Communications
Our customers are solely responsible for their own marketing emails and other communications; we cannot unsubscribe you from their communications. You can unsubscribe from our customers' marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of their emails, or by contacting them directly.
Contact
Joe LapinskasDirector of Marketing & Innovation
QSA Global, Inc.40 North Avenue Burlington, MA 01803
Products
SENTINEL 880 Series
SENTINEL 1075 SCARPro
SENTINEL SENTRY Series
OpenVision DX
QSA Global, Inc. Headquarters40 North AvenueBurlington, MA 01803
Customer Service800-225-1383Send Feedback
© 2020 QSA Global, Inc.
|
Cookie Policy   |
Privacy Policy   |
Terms & Conditions
